Guide to the Bosnia and Herzegovina Political Ephemera Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Bosnia and Herzegovina political ephemera collection
2006-2006
MS 1926
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
(1 box)
The collection comprises campaign brochures, flyers, and posters representing the various political parties that participated in the 2006 October 1st general election to determine the presidency and parliament seats of Bosnia and Herzegovina; entity parliaments for the Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, as well as the Republika Srpska; and canton parliaments.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by name of political party.
Scope and Contents
The collection comprises campaign brochures, flyers, and posters representing the various political parties that participated in the 2006 October 1st general election to determine the presidency and parliament seats of Bosnia and Herzegovina; entity parliaments for the Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, as well as the Republika Srpska; and canton parliaments.
Custodial History
The collection was transferred from the Slavic and East European curator, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Elections -- Bosnia and Herzegovina -- Bosnia and Hercegovina (Federation); Elections -- Bosnia and Herzegovina -- Republika Srpska; Elections -- Bosnia and Herzegovina; Political parties -- Bosnia and Herzegovina; Bosnia and Herzegovina (Bosnia and Herzegovina: Federation); Bosnia and Herzegovina; Republika Srpska (Bosnia and Herzegovina)
- Original Accession
  - Bosanskopodrinjska Narodna Stranka (BPNS), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Centralna Izborna Komisija, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Demokratski Narodni Savez (Democratic People's Alliance), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fondacija Mozaik, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gradanska Demokratska Stranka BiH, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hrvatska Demokratska Unija BiH, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hrvatska Demokratska Zajednica (HDZ) (Croatian Democratic Union of Bosnia and Herzegovina), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Liberalno Demokratska Stranka BiH, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Narodna Stranka Radom (People's Party), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Partija Demokratskog Progresa (Party of Democratic Progress), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pokret Mladih BiH, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Socijal Demokratska Partija BiH (Social Democratic Party), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Socijal Demokratska Unija Patriotski Blok, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stranka Demokratske Akcije (Party of Democratic Action), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stranka Za Bosnu I Hercegovinu (Party for Bosnia and Herzegovina), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)